(This series is produced for entertainment purposes. The characters, actions, locations, and events depicted are fictional
(تم إنتاج هذه السلسلة لأغراض ترفيهية. الشخصيات، والأحداث، والمواقع، والأحداث المصورة خيالية)
and do not allude to any real organization, profession, or group of individuals.
ولا تشير إلى أي منظمة حقيقية أو مهنة أو مجموعة من الأفراد.
This program may contain imagery, sounds, and contents that are inappropriate in terms of behavior, violence, sex, and language.
قد يحتوي هذا البرنامج على صور وأصوات ومحتوى غير مناسب من حيث السلوك والعنف والجنس واللغة.
Viewers under 18 should be advised. (Viewer discretion is advised.)
يجب على المشاهدين الذين تقل أعمارهم عن 18 عامًا إبلاغنا بذلك. (ينصح المشاهدين بتوخي الحذر.)
Can I call you "My Babe"? Because my whole heart I give to you
هل يمكنني أن أناديكِ "حبيبتي"؟ لأن قلبي كله لك.
Can I call you "My Babe"? Because my whole heart I dedicate to you
هل يمكنني أن أناديكِ "حبيبتي"؟ لأن قلبي كله أهديه لكِ.
Whenever I turn, I see you
كلما التفت أراك
Because you are the answer
لأنك أنت الجواب
And I won't give the word "love" to anyone else…
ولن أعطي كلمة "حب" لأي شخص آخر...
Can I call you "My Babe"? Because my whole heart I give to you
هل يمكنني أن أناديكِ "حبيبتي"؟ لأن قلبي كله لك.
Can I call you "My Babe"? Because my whole heart I dedicate to you
هل يمكنني أن أناديكِ "حبيبتي"؟ لأن قلبي كله أهديه لكِ.
Whenever I turn, I see you
كلما التفت أراك
Because you are the answer
لأنك أنت الجواب
And I won't give the word "love" to anyone else, except for you
ولن أعطي كلمة "حب" لأي شخص آخر، إلا لك
Can I call you "My Babe"? Love, love, love
هل يمكنني أن أناديكِ "حبيبتي"؟ مع حبي، مع حبي، مع حبي.
Can I call you "My Babe"?
هل يمكنني أن أناديك بـ "حبيبتي"؟
"Doctor's Mine" (Episode 8)
"منجم الطبيب" (الحلقة 8)
Are you tired?
هل انت متعب؟
Do you want some water?
هل تريد بعض الماء؟
Fine, I'm still okay.
حسنًا، أنا لا أزال بخير.
Hey!! P'Knight, There are a lot of people.
مرحبًا!! P'Knight، هناك الكثير من الناس.
I was just joking.
لقد كنت أمزح فقط.
Did you really think I was going to feed you water?
هل كنت تعتقد حقا أنني سأطعمك الماء؟
Just go on ahead and hike up the mountain.
فقط استمر في المضي قدمًا وتسلق الجبل.
Mild!
خفيف!
Do you want some jelly?
هل تريد بعض الجيلي؟
Yeah, I'll have some.
نعم، سآخذ بعضًا.
Hey, wait a minute! I just asked if you wanted my water.
مهلا، انتظر لحظة! سألتك إن كنت تريد ماءً.
Why didn't you drink my water, Mild?
لماذا لم تشرب الماء الخاص بي يا مايلد؟
Hey!!
يا!!
Oh, Klah.
أوه، كلاه.
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
Don't bother them.
لا تزعجهم.
The snack in your hand...
الوجبة الخفيفة في يدك...
it's probably not as interesting as what those two are about to do.
ربما لا يكون الأمر مثيرًا للاهتمام مثل ما سيفعله هذان الشخصان.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
I just wanted to share it with our friend.
أردت فقط أن أشاركها مع صديقنا.
Let's go back to our place. Come on.
لنعد إلى مكاننا. هيا.
What's wrong with him?
ما به؟
Hey, doctor. How have you been?
أهلاً دكتور، كيف حالك؟
I haven't seen you in a long time.
لم أرك منذ وقت طويل.
Yeah, well... I'm okay.
نعم، حسنًا... أنا بخير.
Whoa... what the hell?
واو... ماذا بحق الجحيم؟
What's up... is it only me who's going to die from being apart?
ما الأمر... هل أنا فقط من سيموت من الانفصال؟
Well, I'm already strong.
حسنًا، أنا قوي بالفعل.
What are you doing, Per?
ماذا تفعل يا بير؟
I'm just looking at someone who's stubborn.
أنا فقط أنظر إلى شخص عنيد.
Your eyes are so swollen, but you're saying you're strong.
عيناك منتفختان جدًا، لكنك تقولين أنك قوية.
You must be crying every day.
يجب أن تبكي كل يوم.
You love me so much, don't you?
أنت تحبني كثيرًا، أليس كذلك؟
Who says I love you?
من قال أني أحبك؟
Even if you didn't tell me, I'd know.
حتى لو لم تخبرني، فأنا سأعرف.
We're a couple now.
نحن زوجين الآن.
And who says we're a couple.
ومن قال أننا زوجين؟
Hey, Doc! Doc!
مرحبا يا دكتور! يا دكتور!
Per, let me go!
بير، دعني أذهب!
But you have to give in first.
ولكن عليك أن تستسلم أولاً.
Say that we're dating.
قل أننا نتواعد.
Per, yeah. I give in.
بير، نعم، أستسلم.
We're dating. We're a couple.
نحن نتواعد. نحن ثنائي.
Are you happy now?
هل انت سعيد الان؟
You're so cute.
أنت لطيف جدًا.
Oh Per! That's enough!
أوه بير! هذا يكفي!
It's not enough. I miss you!
هذا ليس كافيا. أفتقدك!
Oh Per. Why are you so infatuated with me?
يا بير، لماذا أنت معجب بي هكذا؟
I feel like a goldfish is sucking on my head.
أشعر وكأن سمكة ذهبية تمتص رأسي.
You're so cute. I'll be your goldfish.
أنت لطيف جدًا. سأكون سمكتك الذهبية.
Oh, now I'm a catfish. Your whiskers are poking my head.
أوه، الآن أنا سمكة سلور. شواربك تخدش رأسي.
Ahhh, that's enough! Let me go! Ahhh!
آه، هذا يكفي! دعني أذهب! آه!
Doc, wait for me. I have a lot of stuff.
يا دكتور، انتظرني. عندي أشياء كثيرة.
Sir, uhm... all the things that the kids brought over here...
سيدي، أوه... كل الأشياء التي أحضرها الأطفال إلى هنا...
What's up?
ما أخبارك؟
Hey...
يا...
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
I'm fine, bro.
أنا بخير يا أخي.
I'm hungry. Let's go eat.
أنا جائع. هيا بنا نأكل.
Okay, Let's go.
حسنا، دعنا نذهب.
I'm very happy
انا سعيد جدا
that we all got to come and help organize this volunteer camp.
أن نتمكن جميعًا من الحضور والمساعدة في تنظيم هذا المعسكر التطوعي.
This year, the National Park Office has provided assistance to the university,
هذا العام، قدم مكتب المتنزهات الوطنية المساعدة للجامعة،
which is how this project came to be once again.
وهكذا ظهر هذا المشروع مرة أخرى.
It's also an opportunity for everyone to develop in many ways.
وهي أيضًا فرصة للجميع للتطور بعدة طرق.
I want everyone to use the knowledge they've learned
أريد من الجميع أن يستخدموا المعرفة التي تعلموها
to be of the greatest benefit to the villagers here.
ليكون ذلك من أكبر المنفعة لأهل القرية هنا.
Do your best, kids.
افعلوا ما بوسعكم يا أطفال.
Yeah!!!
نعم!!!
Alright everyone, now I'd like to invite the village chief to say a few words to the kids.
حسنًا يا رفاق، الآن أود أن أدعو رئيس القرية ليقول بضع كلمات للأطفال.
Hello, everyone.
أهلا بالجميع.
Hello!
مرحبًا!
I'm the village chief here.
أنا رئيس القرية هنا.
I'm very happy that you've all come to help develop our village.
أنا سعيد جدًا لأنكم جميعًا أتيتم للمساعدة في تطوير قريتنا.
If you need anything, just let me know.
إذا كنت بحاجة إلى أي شيء، فقط أخبرني.
There's also another thing I want to warn you about.
هناك أيضًا شيء آخر أريد أن أحذرك منه.
We believe in ghosts and spirits in this village.
نحن نؤمن بالأشباح والأرواح في هذه القرية.
Doctor...
طبيب...
Per, what's wrong with you?
بير، ما الذي حدث لك؟
Per.
لكل.
I'm scared.
أنا خائفة.
Per!
لكل!
Don't go out of your accommodation at night.
لا تخرج من مكان إقامتك ليلاً.
There are dangerous wild animals here, and the spirits of the forest and mountains too.
هناك حيوانات برية خطيرة هنا، وأرواح الغابة والجبال أيضًا.
Okay, kids, how about this.
حسنًا يا أطفال، ماذا عن هذا؟
Everyone can go and get to work now.
الآن بإمكان الجميع الذهاب إلى العمل.
Is that okay?
هل هذا جيد؟
Yes.
نعم.
Okay, great. Thank you.
حسنًا، رائع. شكرًا لك.
Be careful, It's dangerous at night.
كن حذرا، إنه أمر خطير في الليل.
I'm going to kill the ghost named Per until he's never reborn.
سأقتل الشبح المسمى بير حتى لا يولد من جديد أبدًا.
You're cruel.
أنت قاسي.
Ahhh, Let's get to work…
أه، دعونا نبدأ العمل...
Go to work!
اذهب الى العمل!
How are you?
كيف حالك؟
I'll check your symptoms now.
سأتحقق من أعراضك الآن.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Don't be worried.
لا تقلق.
I'll prescribe some medicine for you.
سأصف لك بعض الأدوية.
Please wait for your medicine in the back.
من فضلك انتظر الدواء الخاص بك في الخلف.
Kan.
يستطيع.
Hey!! Mayo!
مرحبا!! ماي!
Mild, don't cry. It's me, it's me.
يا لطيف، لا تبكي. أنا، أنا.
What are you doing, P' Knight?
ماذا تفعل يا بي نايت؟
Who said I was playing around?
من قال أنني كنت ألعب؟
Can't I just want to be with you?
هل لا أستطيع أن أريد فقط أن أكون معك؟
We haven't talked all day today.
لم نتحدث طيلة اليوم.
Are you addicted to me?
هل أنت مدمن علي؟
It's been a long time.
لقد مر وقت طويل.
So you're just going to stay here all day?
إذن أنت ستبقى هنا طوال اليوم؟
No need to go drinking.
لا داعي للذهاب للشرب.
I don't mind.
أنا لا أمانع.
Mild!
خفيف!
The drinking party is starting!
حفل الشرب بدأ!
Then next time.
ثم المرة القادمة.
I'll be waiting.
سوف انتظر.
Let's go! Cheers, everyone!
هيا بنا! هتاف الجميع!
Bottoms up! Bottoms up!
إلى الأعلى! إلى الأعلى!
Bottoms up?
من الأسفل إلى الأعلى؟
The last one to finish pay us all Korean BBQ.
آخر واحد لإنهاء دفع لنا جميعا الشواء الكوري.
Hey, wait!
مهلا، انتظر!
Did I miss something?
هل فاتني شيء؟
How are you? Are you tired?
كيف حالك؟ هل أنت متعب؟
I'm okay.
انا بخير.
It's been fun.
لقد كان ممتعا.
I haven't done anything like this in a long time.
لم أفعل شيئًا كهذا منذ وقت طويل.
You're doing it so well.
أنت تفعل ذلك بشكل جيد.
I wouldn't be able to build this.
لن أكون قادراً على بناء هذا.
Aw..., so you've been watching me all the time, huh?
أوه... إذًا كنت تراقبني طوال الوقت، أليس كذلك؟
What? It's you.
ماذا؟ أنت.
Every time I turn around, you're always looking at me.
في كل مرة أستدير، تجد نفسك تنظر إليّ دائمًا.
Aw, because when you're treating a patient, it's so charming.
آه، لأنه عندما تعالج مريضًا، يكون الأمر ساحرًا للغاية.
Of course it is.
بالطبع هو كذلك.
I was the star of the medical faculty, you know.
لقد كنت نجم كلية الطب، كما تعلمون.
Everyone says that.
الجميع يقولون ذلك.
I'm annoyed.
أنا منزعج.
Yeah, that's normal. Everyone likes me, you know.
نعم، هذا طبيعي. الجميع يحبني، كما تعلم.
Even that person who just served us water?
حتى ذلك الشخص الذي قدم لنا الماء فقط؟
Oh, Mayo.
أوه، مايو.
He's my patient.
إنه مريضي.
I treated him once,
لقد عالجته مرة واحدة،
so he probably came to say thanks.
فمن المحتمل أنه جاء ليقول شكرًا.
Hmm, you're getting quite popular.
مممم، أنت تحصل على شعبية كبيرة.
I guess I'll have to assert my ownership.
أعتقد أنني سأضطر إلى تأكيد ملكيتي.
Hey Per, Per! Let go!
يا بير، بير! دعني أذهب!
Per! Oh, I'm so embarrassed in front of the spirits of the forest and mountains.
يا إلهي! أشعر بالخجل الشديد أمام أرواح الغابة والجبال.
Why are you embarrassed, Doc?
لماذا أنت محرج يا دكتور؟
Aww, you might not be, but I am.
أوه، ربما لا تكون كذلك، ولكنني كذلك.
Just one more time.
مرة واحدة فقط .
You're late. / The latecomers.
لقد تأخرت. / المتأخرون.
They have to get it. Drink it neat.
عليهم الحصول عليه، وشربه نقيًا.
Go on.
إستمر.
For the latecomers.
للمتأخرين.
Go on, my friend./ Sorry, guys, I'm late.
إستمر ​​يا صديقي./ آسف يا شباب، لقد تأخرت.
You're late, so gonna get it.
لقد تأخرت، لذا سأحصل عليه.
Drink it neat!
اشربه نقيا!
Let's go!
دعنا نذهب!
C'mon, one glass each!
تعالوا، كأس واحد لكل واحد!
Oh.
أوه.
Bottoms up! Bottoms up!
إلى الأعلى! إلى الأعلى!
Wait, you said you quit drinking!
انتظر، لقد قلت أنك توقفت عن الشرب!
I'll drink it for you.
سأشربه لك.
You're so cool!
أنت رائع جدًا!
Per, if you're gonna act like a hero like those two, Just don't.
بير، إذا كنت تريد أن تتصرف كبطل مثل هذين الاثنين، فقط لا تفعل ذلك.
I'll drink it myself.
سأشربه بنفسي.
Mmm, this's it.
ممم، هذا هو.
It has to be like this!
لا بد أن يكون مثل هذا!
You're so cute.
أنت لطيف جدًا.
Hey Per, I'm your brother.
مرحبًا بير، أنا أخوك.
Too sweet!
حلوة جداً!
Who calls their boyfriend "brother"?
من ينادي صديقه بـ "الأخ"؟
Just drink, bro. Don't talk so much.
اشرب بس يا أخي. ما تتكلم كثير.
Bottoms up! Bottoms up!
إلى الأعلى! إلى الأعلى!
Of course, this person will finish it.
بالطبع هذا الشخص سوف ينهي الأمر.
I'm not drunk.
أنا لست في حالة سكر.
If you're not drunk, lift your head up.
إذا لم تكن سكرانًا، ارفع رأسك إلى الأعلى.
Hey, are you not going to let me lean on you anymore?
مهلا، هل لن تسمح لي بالاعتماد عليك بعد الآن؟
No, I'm just going to move a little.
لا، سأتحرك قليلاً فقط.
Want more, doc?
هل تريد المزيد يا دكتور؟
You're trying to get me drunk?
هل تحاول أن تجعلني في حالة سُكر؟
And is that working?
وهل هذا يعمل؟
Sorry. This isn't enough to get me drunk.
آسف. هذا لا يكفي لإسكاتي.
But I'm drunk.
ولكنني في حالة سكر.
If you're drunk, go to sleep.
إذا كنت في حالة سكر، اذهب إلى النوم.
Hey!
يا!
You'll get drunk!
سوف تسكر!
Don't you dare stop me.
لا تجرؤ على ايقافي.
Give it to me.
أعطيني إياه.
You never understand me.
أنت لا تفهمني أبدًا.
Hey!! A drinking circle like this needs some games.
مهلا!! دائرة شرب مثل هذه تحتاج إلى بعض الألعاب.
Klah, help me think of it.
كلا، ساعدني على التفكير في هذا الأمر.
Woah, you're just tossing it to me.
واو، أنت فقط ترميها لي.
How about 'Never Have I Ever'?
ماذا عن "لم أفعل ذلك أبدًا"؟
Yeah, who wants to play?
نعم من يريد اللعب؟
I'm down.
أنا في الأسفل.
Kan, can you walk me to the restroom? It's dark.
كان، هل يمكنك أن تأخذني إلى الحمام؟ إنه مظلم.
Don't go.
لا تذهب.
Per, my friend is a woman. It's dangerous.
بير، صديقتي امرأة. الأمر خطير.
I'm a man who's very drunk and very handsome.
أنا رجل سكران جدًا ووسيم جدًا.
Doctor, if you leave me here, aren't you afraid someone will snatch me away?
دكتور، إذا تركتني هنا، ألا تخاف أن يخطفني أحد؟
Just a moment.
لحظة واحدة.
Are you really dating N'Per?
هل أنت تواعد N'Per حقًا؟
Yeah, I am.
نعم انا كذلك.
Can you even date a guy?
هل يمكنك مواعدة رجل؟
It doesn't matter if I'm dating a guy or a girl.
لا يهم إن كنت أواعد رجلاً أو فتاة.
What matters is if I really like him.
ما يهم هو إذا كنت أحبه حقا.
That's what's important.
هذا هو المهم.
I love you.
أحبك.
But I don't like you.
ولكنني لا أحبك.
I've already told you that.
لقد قلت لك ذلك بالفعل.
Don't do something you'll regret while you're drunk.
لا تفعل شيئًا ستندم عليه وأنت في حالة سُكر.
I know you can't love me,
أعلم أنك لا تستطيع أن تحبني،
but I just want you to know that I love you very much.
لكني أريدك فقط أن تعلم أنني أحبك كثيرًا.
I've been waiting for you for a very long time.
لقد كنت أنتظرك لفترة طويلة جدًا.
Six years, Kan. Six years.
ست سنوات، كان. ست سنوات.
Why have you never looked at me at all?
لماذا لم تنظر إلي مطلقا؟
Natcha, I've already told you that I don't like you.
ناتشا، لقد قلت لك بالفعل أنني لا أحبك.
If you still want to be my friend,
إذا كنت لا تزال تريد أن تكون صديقي،
don't do this.
لا تفعل هذا.
I'm sorry,
أنا آسف،
I'm really sorry.
انا آسف حقا.
Please take care of her for me.
من فضلك اعتني بها من أجلي.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Natcha.
ناتشا.
What have I done?
ماذا فعلت؟
I shouldn't have done it. I don't want to lose him.
ما كان ينبغي لي أن أفعل ذلك. لا أريد أن أخسره.
It's okay. It's okay.
لا بأس. لا بأس.
Even if Kanjan doesn't love you, I love you.
حتى لو كان كانجان لا يحبك، فأنا أحبك.
I don't want to love him as a friend.
لا أريد أن أحبه كصديق.
What's wrong with me?
ماذا بي؟
I met him first.
لقد التقيت به أولاً.
Love is like this.
الحب هو مثل هذا.
But you're good. You're the best, believe me.
لكنك جيد. أنت الأفضل، صدقني.
Kan loves you as a friend.
كان يحبك كصديق.
Give yourself time to move on.
أعطي نفسك الوقت للمضي قدمًا.
Do I really have to move on?
هل يجب علي حقا المضي قدما؟
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Per.
لكل.
What're you doing sitting here all by yourself.
ماذا تفعل جالسا هنا بمفردك؟
Did the drinking party end?
هل انتهى حفل الشرب؟
Not yet.
ليس بعد.
I thought you weren't gonna be here.
اعتقدت أنك لن تكون هنا.
Do you think I'm weak, incompetent, and can't protect myself?
هل تعتقد أنني ضعيف وغير كفء ولا أستطيع حماية نفسي؟
Well, you gave in to her.
حسنًا، لقد استسلمت لها.
I thought you'd be comforting her until morning.
اعتقدت أنك ستواصل مواساتها حتى الصباح.
She's my friend.
إنها صديقتي.
But I'm your husband.
ولكنني زوجك.
Hey, Per, I've been gone for a while. And you're still not done drinking?
أهلاً بير، لقد غبت لفترة. وما زلتَ تشرب؟
Up to you then.
الأمر متروك لك إذن.
And is this your tent?
وهل هذه خيمتك؟
Hold on.
يتمسك.
What?
ماذا؟
You're going to sleep with me?
هل ستنام معي؟
N'Per, I've walked all the way to your tent.
ن'بير، لقد مشيت كل الطريق إلى خيمتك.
I'm probably not here to hang out.
ربما أنا لست هنا لقضاء الوقت.
Let's just sleep.
دعنا ننام فقط.
Wait for me, Doc!
انتظرني يا دكتور!
Doc!
دكتور!
What's wrong with you?
ما مشكلتك؟
Do you know how long it's been since we last saw each other?
هل تعلم كم من الوقت مضى منذ أن رأينا بعضنا البعض آخر مرة؟
Three weeks.
ثلاثة اسابيع.
And do you know how much I've missed you?
و هل تعلم كم اشتقت إليك؟
How would I know, Per?
كيف يمكنني أن أعرف، بير؟
Then do you know we're boyfriends now?
ثم هل تعلم أننا أصبحنا أصدقاء الآن؟
Yeah, that I know, that you and I...
نعم، أنا أعلم، أنك وأنا...
Per, Per, I can't breathe.
بير، بير، لا أستطيع التنفس.
But you started it.
ولكنك بدأت ذلك.
How did I start it?
كيف بدأت ذلك؟
You came to sleep with me.
لقد أتيت لتنام معي.
Did you think I could hold back?
هل كنت تعتقد أنني أستطيع التمسك؟
I just didn't want to sleep in the resthouse.
لم أكن أريد النوم في بيت الراحة.
I wanted to be closer to nature,
أردت أن أكون أقرب إلى الطبيعة،
what's wrong with that?
ما الخطأ في ذلك؟
So, doctor, take it off.
إذن يا دكتور، انزعها.
Why?
لماذا؟
Because my darling wants to feel nature.
لأن حبيبتي تريد أن تشعر بالطبيعة.
How about we sleep naked tonight?
ماذا عن أن ننام عراة الليلة؟
Ahhhh!
آآآآه!
Doc! That hurts!
دكتور! هذا يؤلمني!
Good, it should hurt.
حسنًا، ينبغي أن يؤلم.
You should think like a normal person.
ينبغي عليك أن تفكر مثل أي شخص عادي.
We'd freeze to death.
سوف نتجمد حتى الموت.
That's why we should sleep naked and exercise to get rid of the cold.
لهذا السبب يجب علينا النوم عراة وممارسة الرياضة للتخلص من البرد.
I'm tired.
أنا متعب.
I'm going to sleep.
سأذهب للنوم.
Doctor...
طبيب...
Hmm?
همم؟
I'm glad we're here together now.
أنا سعيد لأننا هنا معًا الآن.
Yeah, I'm glad too.
نعم، أنا سعيد أيضًا.
I love you, Doc.
انا احبك يا دكتور.
I love you too, Per.
انا احبك أيضا، بير.
P' Pat, are you not mad at me anymore?
بي بات، هل لم تعد غاضبا مني بعد الآن؟
Why did you let me drop you off?
لماذا سمحت لي أن أنزلك؟
What's the big deal?
ما هو الأمر الكبير؟
We're a couple.
نحن زوجين.
Can't you do just this one thing for me?
هل يمكنك أن تفعل هذا الشيء فقط من أجلي؟
Let me ask you something.
دعني أسألك شيئا.
All the time we've been together,
طوال الوقت الذي كنا فيه معًا،
have you ever really loved me?
هل أحببتني حقا؟
Or did you just date me because you wanted a personal servant?
أم أنك كنت تواعدني فقط لأنك تريد خادمًا شخصيًا؟
Because you wanted information on Mild?
لأنك أردت معلومات عن Mild؟
What am I to you?
ماذا أنا بالنسبة لك؟
Tum, don't you dare use that tone with me.
توم، لا تجرؤ على استخدام هذه النبرة معي.
And did I ever ask you to date me first?
وهل طلبت منك أن تواعدني أولاً؟
You can't even get anything I ask you to do.
لا يمكنك حتى الحصول على أي شيء أطلب منك القيام به.
Seriously, what's the point of us even though we're still together?
بجدية، ما الفائدة من وجودنا حتى لو كنا لا نزال معًا؟
I should've listened to Klah from the start.
كان ينبغي لي أن أستمع إلى كلاه منذ البداية.
You never truly loved me.
أنت لم تحبني بصدق أبدًا.
Tonklah Tonklah Tonklah!
تونكلاه تونكلاه تونكلاه!
Mild Mild Mild!!
خفيف خفيف خفيف!!
Your life is all about your friends.
حياتك كلها تتعلق بأصدقائك.
If you love your friend so much, why don't you just go live with them?
إذا كنت تحب صديقك كثيرًا، فلماذا لا تذهب للعيش معه؟
Sure, I'll go.
بالتأكيد سأذهب.
If you walk out, we're over.
إذا خرجت، سننتهي.
Fine, that's what I want anyway.
حسنًا، هذا ما أريده على أي حال.
Fine! Just go!
حسناً! فقط اذهب!
Go wherever you want.
اذهب إلى أي مكان تريد.
I can find someone a million times better than you.
أستطيع أن أجد شخصًا أفضل منك بمليون مرة.
What's up?
ما أخبارك؟
Hey Klah, let's have a drink together first.
مرحبًا كلاه، دعنا نتناول مشروبًا معًا أولًا.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
I just broke up with P' Pat.
لقد انفصلت للتو عن بي بات.
I just realized everything you warned me about was true.
لقد أدركت للتو أن كل ما حذرتني منه كان صحيحًا.
She broke up with you?
هل انفصلت عنك؟
No, I broke up with her.
لا، لقد انفصلت عنها.
I don't know why I should be with someone who doesn't love me.
لا أعلم لماذا يجب أن أكون مع شخص لا يحبني.
So, she told you?
فهل أخبرتك؟
I don't want to think about it anymore.
لا أريد أن أفكر في هذا الأمر بعد الآن.
Yeah, it's okay.
نعم، لا بأس.
Stay with me.
ابقى معي.
It might be a little late,
ربما يكون متأخرا قليلا،
but I just realized I can live without P' Pat.
ولكنني أدركت للتو أنني أستطيع العيش بدون بي بات.
But if I don't have you, I'd be sad more than this.
ولكن إذا لم أكن معك، فإنني سأحزن أكثر من هذا.
I'll be here for you,
سأكون هنا من أجلك
for as long as you need me.
طالما كنت في حاجة لي.
Hey P' Fern!
مرحباً بي فيرن!
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Are you alright,
هل انت بخير؟
are you hurt?
هل انت مصاب؟
Fern, Are you okay?
فيرن، هل أنت بخير؟
Mild.
خفيف.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Does it hurt? Are you alright?
هل يؤلمك؟ هل أنت بخير؟
What the hell are you doing?
ماذا تفعل بحق الجحيم؟
P'Fern was about to fall, so I went to help her. It's nothing.
كادت بِفرن أن تسقط، فذهبتُ لمساعدتها. لم يحدث شيء.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
He went out to help you, and instead of thanking him...
لقد خرج لمساعدتك، وبدلا من أن تشكره...
Fern was startled, didn't you see?
لقد فزعت فيرن، ألم ترى ذلك؟
P'Knight, it's okay.
بي'نايت، لا بأس.
I'm okay.
انا بخير.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
But Mild...
ولكن معتدل...
Please.
لو سمحت.
I want you to treat my wound.
أريدك أن تعالج جرحي.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Does it hurt?
هل يؤلمك؟
It's okay. Not much.
لا بأس، ليس كثيرًا.
Why did you go to help him, huh?
لماذا ذهبت لمساعدته؟
P'Knight, someone was in danger.
بي'نايت، كان هناك شخص في خطر.
Besides, I'm a doctor.
وبالإضافة إلى ذلك، أنا طبيب.
I have to help no matter who it is.
يجب علي أن أساعد بغض النظر عمن كان.
When you date a doctor, you should get used to this kind of thing.
عندما تواعد طبيبًا، يجب عليك أن تعتاد على هذا النوع من الأشياء.
I'm so sorry.
أنا آسف جدا.
For making you worry.
لأنه يجعلك قلقًا.
But P'Fern really isn't at fault here.
لكن P'Fern ليس مخطئًا حقًا هنا.
Mild,
خفيف،
thank you for helping me.
شكرا لمساعدتي.
And I'm sorry if I ever said anything or thought anything bad about you.
وأنا آسف إذا قلت أي شيء أو فكرت في أي شيء سيء عنك.
That's all I wanted to say.
هذا كل ما أردت قوله.
P'Fern.
ب'فيرن.
I'm sorry, too. For everything.
أنا آسف أيضًا. على كل شيء.
Let's go, Fern.
دعنا نذهب، فيرن.
I've cleared things up with P'Fern.
لقد قمت بتوضيح الأمور مع P'Fern.
Have you tried talking to P'Night properly?
هل حاولت التحدث مع P'Night بشكل صحيح؟
I already cleared things up with her a long time ago.
لقد قمت بتوضيح الأمور معها منذ وقت طويل.
I told her that we're just friends with benefits.
قلت لها أننا مجرد أصدقاء مع بعض الفوائد.
But what you said, did you really talk to her nicely.
ولكن ما قلته، هل تحدثت معها بشكل جيد حقًا؟
Or really listen to her feelings?
أم نستمع حقًا إلى مشاعرها؟
No matter what she says, I won't change my mind.
مهما قالت فلن أغير رأيي.
P'Knight, do you know how to carry the feeling of loving someone all by yourself?
بي'نايت، هل تعرف كيف تحمل شعور حب شخص ما بمفردك؟
The pain is endless.
الألم لا نهاية له.
So I went to listen to them, what's next?
فذهبت لأستمع إليهم، ماذا بعد؟
Just let them express all their feelings.
فقط دعهم يعبرون عن كل مشاعرهم.
After this, what happens?
بعد هذا ماذا يحدث؟
They've already tried their best.
لقد بذلوا قصارى جهدهم بالفعل.
A clear rejection and a good farewell are important.
الرفض الواضح والوداع الجيد أمران مهمان.
And you're okay with that?
و أنت موافق على ذلك؟
At least you two won't have any lingering feelings.
على الأقل لن يكون بينكما أي مشاعر باقية.
Okay, I'll find a chance to go talk to them.
حسنًا، سأبحث عن فرصة للتحدث معهم.
That's great.
هذا عظيم.
I think it's just a fever from the changing weather.
أعتقد أنها مجرد حمى بسبب تغير الطقس.
Nothing to be too worried about.
لا داعي للقلق كثيرا.
You can pick up your medicine at the back later.
يمكنك الحصول على الدواء الخاص بك في الخلف لاحقًا.
Welcome.
مرحباً.
P'Kan.
ب'كان.
Oh, Mayo. What's up?
أوه مايو، ما الأمر؟
I just saw that you were so busy that we didn't get to talk much.
لقد رأيت للتو أنك كنت مشغولاً للغاية ولم نتمكن من التحدث كثيرًا.
Yeah, that's right.
نعم، هذا صحيح.
How are you? The results from the last check-up...
كيف حالك؟ نتائج الفحص الأخير...
Uh... well...
أوه... حسنًا...
Is the person who did this to you still bothering you?
هل الشخص الذي فعل بك هذا لا يزال يزعجك؟
He... so...
هو... إذن...
Yo.
هم.
P'Guy.
بي جاي.
I think we should all calm down.
أعتقد أننا جميعا يجب أن نهدأ.
Um... maybe we should talk things through slowly?
اممم... ربما يجب علينا أن نتحدث في الأمور ببطء؟
Who the hell are you?
من أنت بحق الجحيم؟
I'm senior.
أنا كبير السن.
I don't think you should be using that word with me.
لا أعتقد أنه يجب عليك استخدام هذه الكلمة معي.
Don't be nosy.
لا تكن فضوليًا.
Hey! Let him go!
مهلا! دعه يذهب!
He doesn't want to go with you. I don't think you have the right to do this!
لا يريد الذهاب معك. لا أعتقد أن لديك الحق في فعل هذا!
Why are you butting in?
لماذا تتدخل؟
Because I'm the one taking care of him.
لأنني أنا من يعتني به.
Because of your bad actions.
بسبب أفعالك السيئة.
And he's my new boyfriend.
وهو صديقي الجديد.
Please stop bothering me.
من فضلك توقف عن ازعاجي.
His new guy is better. Can't you accept that?
صديقه الجديد أفضل. ألا يمكنكِ تقبّل ذلك؟
Hey!
يا!
Whoa!! What's going on?
واو!! ماذا يحدث؟
Hey Per!
مرحبا بير!
He's mine, don't you dare interfere.
إنه ملكي، لا تجرؤ على التدخل.
Got it?
فهمتها؟
Yes.
نعم.
Mayo, are you hurt? Are you okay?
مايو، هل أنتِ مصابة؟ هل أنتِ بخير؟
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
Let me take a look.
دعني ألقي نظرة.
Come sit down.
تعال واجلس.
That's enough.
هذا يكفي.
Let him do it himself.
دعه يفعل ذلك بنفسه.
Not yet. Just a little bit more and it will be done.
ليس بعد. فقط القليل وسينتهي الأمر.
I'll go get you some medicine.
سأذهب لأحضر لك بعض الدواء.
But... Doctor.
ولكن... يا دكتور.
Doctor...
طبيب...
If it hurts, tell me.
إذا كان الأمر مؤلمًا، أخبرني.
Yes.
نعم.
And don't use your arm for a while. Okay?
ولا تستخدم ذراعك لفترة من الوقت. حسنًا؟
Yes. Thank you, P'Kan.
نعم، شكرًا لك، بي كان.
Umm.
اممم.
Per, Per, wait for me.
بير، بير، انتظرني.
Per, what's wrong?
بير، ما الخطب؟
Are you mad at me?
هل أنت غاضب مني؟
You don't pay attention to me.
أنت لا تهتم بي.
Oh, I'm sorry.
أوه، أنا آسف.
Let's make up, okay?
دعونا نتصالح، حسنًا؟
Per, I'm embarrassed.
بير، أنا محرج.
Per,
لكل،
Per, let me go.
بير، دعني أذهب.
Are P' Kan and P' Per...
هل P' Kan و P' Per...
Husband and wife.
زوج وزوجة.
Uh, Mayo, what I mean is...
أوه، مايو، ما أقصده هو...
It's okay.
لا بأس.
What is meant to be ours will always be ours.
ما كان من المفترض أن يكون لنا سوف يظل لنا دائمًا.
What did he say?
ماذا قال؟
Per, let me tell you this right now.
بير، اسمح لي أن أخبرك بهذا الآن.
Besides you, I really don't want anyone else.
بجانبك، أنا حقا لا أريد أي شخص آخر.
I've given my heart to you only.
لقد أعطيت قلبي لك فقط.
Per, Per, Per!
من أجل، من أجل، من أجل!
Per, let me go!
بير، دعني أذهب!
I'm so stupid, just like Klah said.
أنا غبي جدًا، تمامًا كما قال كلاه.
I was stuck in a toxic relationship and didn't want to leave.
لقد كنت عالقًا في علاقة سامة ولم أكن أرغب في المغادرة.
People who are stuck in a toxic relationship don't even realize it.
الأشخاص الذين وقعوا في علاقة سامة لا يدركون ذلك.
So I looked stupid, right? I looked stupid?
إذًا بدوتُ غبيًا، أليس كذلك؟ بدوتُ غبيًا؟
No, You're the most normal you've ever been right now.
لا، أنت أكثر طبيعية مما كنت عليه الآن.
Ohh, so before this, I did look stupid then.
أوه، قبل هذا، كنت أبدو غبيًا حينها.
Huh? You said it yourself.
هاه؟ لقد قلت ذلك بنفسك.
Hey, you ass!
مهلا، أيها الحمار!
Alright, alright, everyone, please listen up.
حسنًا، حسنًا، يا رفاق، أرجوكم استمعوا.
My younger brother has something he wants to say to someone.
لدى أخي الأصغر شيئًا يريد أن يقوله لشخص ما.
Woah, bro, that's so sweet.
واو، أخي، هذا لطيف جدًا.
The heroine let's stand right in front.
البطلة دعونا نقف في المقدمة مباشرة.
Who's the heroine?
من هي البطلة؟
It might not sound good, but I want you to listen.
ربما لا يبدو هذا جيدًا، لكني أريدك أن تستمع.
Baby baby babe, I thought it was just a fairy tale.
يا حبيبتي يا حبيبتي، اعتقدت أنها مجرد قصة خيالية.
Baby baby babe, not a dream, you're right in front of me
يا حبيبتي يا حبيبتي، ليس حلمًا، أنت أمامي مباشرةً
I don't know how to thank you enough, For us having each other today.
لا أعرف كيف أشكركم بما فيه الكفاية، على وجودنا معًا اليوم.
Can I call you "My Babe"? Because my whole heart I give to you.
هل يمكنني أن أناديكِ "حبيبتي"؟ لأن قلبي كله لك.
Because my whole heart I dedicate to you.
لأن قلبي كله أهديه لكِ.
Whenever I turn, I see you. Because you are the answer.
كلما التفتُّ أراك. لأنك أنت الجواب.
And I won't give the word "love" to anyone else, except for you.
ولن أعطي كلمة "حب" لأي شخص آخر، إلا لك.
P'Knight, are you going to propose to my friend?
بي'نايت، هل ستتقدم لخطبة صديقي؟
Yeah, it's true. We're giving him to you!
نعم، هذا صحيح. سنعطيه لك!
Something like this, I need Mild to hear it alone.
شيء من هذا القبيل، أحتاج إلى أن أسمعه بمفردي.
Can you come with me for a while?
هل يمكنك أن تأتي معي لبعض الوقت؟
I have something I want to show you.
عندي شيء أريد أن أعرضه لك.
Where are you going?
إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
Hey, Mild!
مهلا، ميلد!
Just for a moment.
فقط للحظة واحدة.
Hey, hey, guys...
مهلا، مهلا، يا شباب...
Cheers!
هتافات!
Bottoms up, guys.
إلى الأسفل، يا شباب.
Mild,
خفيف،
I know I'm not a good person.
أعلم أنني لست شخصًا جيدًا.
I have a lot of flaws and I've done a lot of stupid things.
لدي الكثير من العيوب وقد فعلت الكثير من الأشياء الغبية.
But I want you to know that I really love you.
ولكن أريدك أن تعرف أنني أحبك حقًا.
Umm, I knows.
اممم، أنا أعلم.
There's one question I've wanted to ask you for a long time.
هناك سؤال واحد أردت أن أسألك إياه منذ وقت طويل.
Will you be my boyfriend?
هل ستكون صديقي؟
Can you give me a chance? Be my boyfriend, okay?
هل يمكنك أن تمنحني فرصة؟ كن صديقي، حسنًا؟
Um.
واحد.
Really?
حقًا؟
Yes.
نعم.
Thank you. Thank you so much. I love you.
شكراً جزيلاً. أحبك.
I can't breathe P'Knight.
لا أستطيع التنفس يا بي'نايت.
Umm. I know.
اممم. انا أعلم.
I'm so happy.
انا سعيد للغاية.
I didn't think I'd have a day like this.
لم أكن أعتقد أنني سأحظى بيوم مثل هذا.
I don't want to make you uncomfortable.
لا أريد أن أجعلك تشعر بعدم الارتياح.
I'm not uncomfortable at all.
أنا لست غير مرتاحة على الإطلاق.
You've shown me how much you love me.
لقد أظهرت لي كم تحبني.
You can't stop smiling. What makes you so happy?
لا يمكنك التوقف عن الابتسام. ما الذي يجعلك سعيدًا جدًا؟
I'm really happy.
أنا سعيد حقا.
Do you know how long I've been secretly looking at you?
هل تعلم كم من الوقت وأنا أنظر إليك سراً؟
Since you started dating P'Ploy?
هل بدأت مواعدة ب'بلوي؟
Yeah, that's really when it was.
نعم، هذا هو الوقت الذي كان فيه حقًا.
But Mild, do you know?
ولكن يا ميلد، هل تعلم؟
By the time I found out that Mud liked Ploy, I was already with her.
بحلول الوقت الذي اكتشفت فيه أن مود تحب بلوي، كنت بالفعل معها.
When I found out, I tried to stop contacting Ploy, tried to distance myself from her.
عندما اكتشفت ذلك، حاولت التوقف عن الاتصال بـ "بلوي"، وحاولت أن أبتعد عنها.
I don't know what other people might think.
لا أعلم ماذا قد يفكر الآخرون.
But Mud, he's my only close friend.
لكن مود هو صديقي الوحيد المقرب.
But this isn't your fault.
ولكن هذا ليس خطأك.
Don't think you're to blame.
لا أعتقد أنك المسؤول.
Hmm.
همم.
Mild,
خفيف،
I have to admit, I had feelings for you while I was dating Ploy.
يجب أن أعترف، لقد كانت لدي مشاعر تجاهك عندما كنت أواعد بلوي.
Stop feeling guilty about it.
توقف عن الشعور بالذنب حيال ذلك.
It was a long time ago.
لقد كان ذلك منذ زمن طويل.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
That's why when I saw you again in university.
ولهذا السبب رأيتك مرة أخرى في الجامعة.
I sometimes thought maybe this was destiny giving me a second chance.
اعتقدت في بعض الأحيان أن هذا ربما كان القدر يمنحني فرصة ثانية.
The spider walked clumsily. When it was two o'clock, it clutched, clutched.
مشى العنكبوت بخطواتٍ خرقاء. وعندما بلغت الساعة الثانية، تشبث به بشدة.
Don't you see he's uncomfortable?
ألا ترى أنه غير مرتاح؟
P'Knight, do you know that I've had a crush on you since the first day we met?
بي'نايت، هل تعلم أنني معجب بك منذ اليوم الأول الذي التقينا فيه؟
Really?
حقًا؟
How can I do? You're so cool.
كيف يمكنني أن أفعل ذلك؟ أنت رائع جدًا.
Mild,
خفيف،
To be honest.
صراحة.
I want you to be mine.
أريدك أن تكون لي.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Did I make you feel bad?
هل جعلتك تشعر بالسوء؟
Stop apologizing.
توقف عن الاعتذار
It's just like what you said that night.
إنه مثل ما قلته تلك الليلة.
Start over with me.
إبدأ معي من جديد.